$obody_option_refit	Enable ORefit
$obody_option_nipple_sliders_orefit	Enable ORefit nipple morphing
$obody_option_nipple	Enable nipple randomization
$obody_option_genitals	Enable genitals randomization
$obody_option_performance_mode	Enable Performance Mode
$obody_option_force_preset_application_immediate	Force immediate preset application
$obody_option_legacy_storage_util_usage	Enable legacy StorageUtil usage
$obody_option_preset_key	Presets list key
$obody_option_reset_distribution	Reset all distributed presets
$obody_message_box_option_yes	Yes
$obody_message_box_option_no	No
$obody_message_performance_mode	Performance mode will be enabled. This might result in more frequent crashes. Refer to the mod page for more info.\n\nIt is NOT recommended to turn on Performance Mode unless you know what you are doing.\n\nIf you want to proceed, click Accept.
$obody_highlight_refit	Makes it so that when an actor is clothed, sliders are changed to simulate the effect clothes have on the different body parts. Works fine with CBBE and UNP based bodies, including CBBE 3BA and BHUNP from my tests. Disable if you get weird results. Character redressing is required for changes to this setting to take effect.
$obody_highlight_nipple_sliders_orefit	If you get sunken or weird nipples/areolas with ORefit, turn off this option to alleviate the problem. Character redressing is required for this to take effect.
$obody_highlight_nipple	Randomizes nipples with procedural generation. Supposedly only works in CBBE based bodies.
$obody_highlight_genitals	Randomizes genitals with procedural generation. Supposedly only works in CBBE 3BA body.
$obody_highlight_performance_mode	With performance mode enabled, you may see body morphs being applied to the NPCs when you meet them for the first time, which can look jarring. However, this happens very rarely, and only when you meet them for the first time! Performance mode enabled may also result in frequent crashes, please refer to the mod page for more information. If you turn off Performance Mode, it may result in stutters/FPS dips in large mod lists or older hardware setups. It is recommended to keep it off for most cases.
$obody_highlight_force_application_immediate	Due to a Racemenu/SSE Engine Fixes bug, sometimes the preset application from the preset list menu is not visually immediate. OBody works around this by redressing the main outfit piece of the character, which forces the new body morphs to apply immediately. If you don't like the visual effect this causes, turn this option off.
$obody_highlight_legacy_storage_util_usage	Before version 4.4.0 of OBody NG, the preset assigned to an NPC was saved using only StorageUtil. Now, OBody NG stores the preset assignment to its own SKSE cosave. For backwards compatibility with mods that read the preset assignment saved using StorageUtil, preset assignments are still saved using StorageUtil when this option is enabled. Disabling this option will reduce the size of your saves slightly, but may cause incompatibilities with older mods.
$obody_highlight_preset_key	Set the key which shows the menu of all installed presets.\nIf an NPC is in your crosshair, it will apply the preset to the NPC. If an NPC is NOT in your crosshair, it will apply the preset to your Player Character.\nSet to Esc to unbind.
$obody_highlight_reset_distribution	Reset the presets that have been distributed to NPCs. This will respect the rules you set in the JSON configuration. Please do this on a cell with no other NPCs or with as few NPCs as possible, such as a player home. Also please note this will only take effect after you save and then reload the game.
$obody_message_reset_distribution	All presets that have been distributed to NPCs will be reset. Your JSON configuration rules will be respected.\n\nPLEASE do this on a cell with no other NPCs or with as few NPCs as possible, such as a player home or even a dungeon.\n\nYou will need to save and exit the game afterwards. Do you want to proceed?
$obody_message_reset_distribution_success	OBody NG will reset the presets that have been distributed.\n\n PLEASE SAVE THE GAME AND EXIT THE GAME NOW! Then start Skyrim and reload your save again. This is needed for the reset to work!
$obody_search_presets	Search Presets
$obody_reset_morphs_button	Reset Morphs
$obody_current_preset	Current Preset
$obody_none	None
$obody_skse_menu_framework_failure  SKSE Menu Framework was not found, which is needed to display the OBody preset selection menu. This means you didn't install SKSE Menu Framework or installed it incorrectly. Please exit the game now and refer to the mod page for instructions.
$obody_preset_list_failure  A critical error has occurred while parsing the Bodyslide presets files. This most likely means you have a corrupt bodyslide preset, or a bodyslide preset where the name contains special/incompatible characters. As a result, the presets list in the OBody menu will be empty. Please exit the game now and refer to the OBody NG mod page for more information.
$obody_presets_tab	Preset Selection
$obody_config_viewer_tab	JSON Config Viewer
$obody_expand_all	Expand All
$obody_collapse_all	Collapse All
$obody_copy_json	Copy JSON